Guide to the Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
Moog, Robert papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
8629
Bob (Robert) Moog
Circa 250 cubic feet.
Audio Recordings, Computer Media, Correspondence, Financial Records, Legal Documents, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Newspapers, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection contains business documents, correspondence, engineering plans and schematics, audio and video recordings, photographs, instruments and instrument components, and other personal papers documenting his work as an engineer and electronic music pioneer.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Robert Moog, founder of Moog Music, was an American engineer and pioneer of electronic music, best known as the inventor of the Moog synthesizer.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection contains business documents, correspondence, engineering plans and schematics, audio and video recordings, photographs, instruments and instrument components, and other personal papers documenting his work as an engineer and electronic music pioneer.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Moog, Bob (Robert) (Robert); Moog, Bob (Robert)
Subjects:
Avant-garde (Music).; Computer music.; Computer sound processing.; Electronic music.; Electronic musical instruments.; Keyboard instrument music.; Moog synthesizer.; Musical instruments.; Synthesizer music.; Synthesizer (Musical instrument).; Music and technology.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to boxes, 23-25, 51, and 57, as well as folders 36, 40, and 41 of box 58, restricted to the permission of the curator.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Personal Papers
Series II. Correspondence
Series III. Business Documents
Series IV. Schematics, Circuit Notes, and Layouts
Series V. Events
Series VI. Technical Articles
Series VII. Clippings
Series VIII. Photographs and Slides
a. Bob Moog
1. Moog Family
b. Associates
c. Events
d. Instruments
1. Studios
2. Theremin
e. Factories
f. Miscellaneous
g. Slides
Series IX. Ephemera
Series X. Media
a. CDs
1. Commercial CD
2. Non-Commercial CD
b. Magnetic Tape
1. Commercial Cassette
2. Non-Commercial Cassette
3. DAT Tape
4. 8 Track Tape
5. Open-Reel Tape
c. Phonograph Records
1. Vinyl
2. Shellac
3. Other Types
d. Video
1. VHS
2. DVD
3. U-Matic
4. Betacam
5. Other Types
e. Film
f. Software
1. Floppy Disk
2. CD
3. Zip Disk
CONTAINER LIST
- Personal Papers, 1957-2004
  Includes college notebooks, personal finance, and articles/notes related to personal interests and activities.
  Arranged chronologically, except where noted otherwise.
  - Personal finances, 1966-1983 (Box 57)
    Contains bills, check stubs, and bank statements.
    Access to box 57 restricted to the permission of the curator.
  - Personal finances, 1983-2004 (Box 24)
    Contains bills, bank statements, taxes, and life insurance/health information.
    Access to box 24 restricted to the permission of the curator.
  - Cornell papers, 1957-1965 (Box 58)
    Includes notebooks, assignments, and readings from Moog's years at Cornell. Includes his 1965 thesis as well as his BA diploma from Queen's College.
    Lecture notes, notebooks, and assignments arranged by course, as per original order.
    Access to folders 36 and 40-41 restricted to the permission of the curator.
  - Personal papers, 1960-2004 (Box 59)
    Contains: articles and notes related to various interests and activities of Moog's including: political organizing with the ACLU; pamphlets from Florence Moog's memorial as well as a selection of her writings; documents pertaining to Moog genealogy; and travel ephemera.
    Arranged by subject.
  - Cornell diploma, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Columbia diploma, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - War bond, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1942-2005
  Alphabetical files (boxes 60-61) includes product inquiries, fan mail, catalog requests, invitations, greeting cards, and personal correspondence. Includes handwritten and typewritten letters, faxes, printed emails, photocopies, and carbon copies.
  Arranged alphabetically by last name of correspondent (or corporate name where applicable).
  - A-M, 1961-2005 (Box 60)
  - M-Z, 1961-2005 (Box 61)
    Also includes business cards, address lists, and correspondence with individuals whose last names could not be determined.
  - Florence Moog, 1942-1987 (Box 62)
    Contains correspondence between Florence Moog and various members of the Moog family (including Robert) as well as correspondence between Florence and friends.
  - Moog Family, 1957-1975 (Box 69)
    Contains correspondence between Moog and various family members, primarily Shirleigh Moog.
    Arranged by year.
- Business Documents, 1954-2011
  Includes financial records, meeting notes and minutes, phone logs, production notes and planning, press releases, company newsletters, product manuals and advertisements for companies Moog operated or was employed by.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Bills and expenses, 1975-1989 (Box 51)
    Contains bills, petty cash receipts, and expenditures (1976-1979, 1982-1989).
    Access to box 51 restricted to the permission of the curator.
  - Business records, 1960-1983 (Box 47)
    Contains R.A. Moog Co., Moog muSonics, and Moog Music/Norlin business documents, including meeting minutes, press releases, sales reports, memos, phone logs, and documentation of product planning, engineering, and production.
  - Business records, 1980-1987 (Box 48)
    Contains Big Briar, Crumar, Synton, and Kurzweil business documents, including meeting minutes, press releases, sales reports, memos, phone logs, and documentation of product planning, engineering, and production. Also contains 1983-1984 business correspondence.
  - Business records, 1987-1998 (Box 49)
    Contains Big Briar, Kurzweil, and Van Koevering business documents, including meeting minutes, press releases, sales reports, memos, phone logs, and documentation of product planning, engineering, and production.
  - Business records, 1998-2005 (Box 27)
    Contains Big Briar, Van Koevering, and Moog Music business documents, including meeting minutes, press releases, sales reports, memos, phone logs, and documentation of product planning, engineering, and production. Also contains documentation of trademark disputes regarding the Moog company name.
  - Invoices and bills, 1968-2003 (Box 50)
    Contains invoices and packing slips (1968-1999) and bills/receipts (1990-2003). Invoices for 1983-1984 are filed in the "Business Correspondence" section of box 48.
  - Manuals, 1954-1987 (Box 52)
    Contains owner's manuals, service manuals, and rough drafts of manuals.
    Additional drafts of manuals for certain products are present in Series IV.
  - Manuals, brochures and catalogs, 1957-2011 (Box 53)
    Manuals (1985-2000, folders 1-15); catalogs, brochures, advertisements, price lists, and newsletters (1957-2011).
  - Quality Works Together advertisement, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Poster-sized advertisement for R.A. Moog and Magnetic Recording Systems, Inc (MRS)
  - Shareholders' agreements, finances, miscellaneous notes, 1967-1973 (Box 25)
    Contains financial records, legal correspondence, stock transfers, and other records documenting the sale of Moog to Waytena and subsequently to Norlin. Also contains undated notes and miscellaneous tax documents dated 1980-1999.
    Access to box 25 restricted to the permission of the curator.
  - Taxes and bank statements, 1981-1986 (Box 23)
    Contains check stubs and bank statements (1981-1987) and taxes (1976-1982).
    Access to box 23 restricted to the permission of the curator.
- Schematics, Circuit Notes, and Layouts
  Includes hand drawn and printed schematics, notes, PCB and panel layouts for circuits developed primarily in the 1960s-1970s. Includes custom designs and modifications for individuals including Wendy Carlos, Keith Emerson, Jan Hammer, Eddie Harris, John Eaton, and Max Brand. Includes associated correspondence with collaborators and customers where applicable.
  Arranged alphabetically by project/product name, last name (where project was commissioned or collaborated on), or manufacturer (where files are neither Moog nor Big Briar, i.e.. Maestro, Hammond, Fairlight, etc.). Within each subseries files are arranged chronologically.
  - Arp String Ensemble
    - SM-005 - String Ensemble-Micromoog box specifications, 1976-03 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - String Ensemble-Micromoog - trig box, 1976-03 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Michael Boddicker
    - Michael Boddicker, Undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Harald Bode
    - 6552 Frequency Shifter, 1967-01-1969-05 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Bode Frequency Shifter, 1967-06-1973-08 (Box 34, Folder 1C)
    - 6552 Bode dome filter, 1968-07 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - New Bode supply 1 of 2, 1968-10-1969-11 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - New Bode supply 2 of 2, 1968-10-1969-11 (Box 34, Folder 1B)
    - Bode Frequency Shifter - Prints 1 of 2, 1972-02-1974-12 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Bode Frequency Shifter - Prints 2 of 2, 1972-02-1974-12 (Mapcase-folder 1B)
    - Bode Frequency Shifter work from 12-72, 1972-12 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Bode Frequency Shifter - 1630 1 of 2, 1973-10 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Bode Frequency Shifter - 1630 2 of 2, 1973-10 (Box 34, Folder 1A)
    - Bode Frequency Shifter 1 of 2, 1973-12-09-1976-04 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Bode Frequency Shifter 2 of 2, 1973-12-09-1976-04 (Mapcase-folder 1A)
    - 1630 Frequency Shifter Folkman, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 1630 Bode Frequency Shifter calibration procedure, 1975-05 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - 6552 Frequency Shifter, Undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Bode models 6401 and 6402 ring modulators - operating/service instructions, Undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Mark Boyd
    - Mark Boyd, 1993-03-1993-06 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - M. Boyd user interface simulation 1 of 2, 1993-06-18 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - M. Boyd user interface simulation 2 of 2, 1993-06-18 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Max Brand
    - Max Brand synthesizer 1 of 2, 1954-1975 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Max Brand synthesizer 2 of 2, 1954-1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Brand harness, subharmonic CEM, switching 1 of 2, 1966-1971 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Brand harness, subharmonic CEM, switching 2 of 2, 1966-1971 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Max Brand - ICA modifications of modules, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Wendy Carlos
    - Carlos system 1 of 2, Spring (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Carlos system 2 of 2, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Carlos touch sensitive envelope generator - Carlos master oscillator bank, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      Includes letter from Carlos to Moog.
    - Rebuilding of Carlos system, 1968-09 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Carlos, 1973-01 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Carlos A-440, Undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Carlos toe system, Undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Central Missouri State University
    - Keyboard for Central Missouri State University, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Touch sensitive keyboard 0170-012 1 of 2, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Touch sensitive keyboard 0170-012 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Joel Chadabe
    - Chadabe frequency divider, 1970-04 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Chadabe single step sequencer, 1970-09 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Chadabe 1 of 2, Undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Chadabe 2 of 2, Undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Chadabe portamento module 1 of 2, Undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Chadabe portamento module 2 of 2, Undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Chadabe signal router - 290-048 1 of 2, Undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Chadabe signal router - 290-048 2 of 2, Undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Classroom Synthesizer, 1970-08-1970-09
    - Classroom Synthesizer, 1970-08 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Classroom Synthesizer 1 of 2, 1970-08 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Classroom Synthesizer 2 of 2, 1970-08 (Mapcase-folder 2A)
    - Classroom Synthesizer 1 of 2, 1970-09 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Classroom Synthesizer 2 of 2, 1970-09 (Mapcase-folder 2B)
    - Classroom Mixer Synth, Undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Billy Cobham, 1970-10-02
    - Billy Cobham - Addition of LED to 912, 1970-10-02 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Cordovox, 1974-05-1976-11
    - Cordovox interface 1 of 2, 1974-05 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Cordovox interface 2 of 2, 1974-05 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    - Cordovox notes and correspondence, 1976-11 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Crumar Spirit, 1982-02-09
    - Crumar Spirit panel transparencies, 1982-02-09 (Mapcase-folder 21)
      Mailed from Crumar to Big Briar in cardboard mailing tube.
  - Neil Diamond, 1976-02
    - Freeman modifications for Neil Diamond, 1976-02 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Distortion, 1977-04-1990-12-23
    - Distortion - CMOS amp, 1977-04 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Distortion - FET as resistor, 1977-04 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Distortion - NMOS amp, 1977-04 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Distortion - PMOS amp, 1977-04 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Keith Emerson
    Original folder labeled "Out-of-pocket expenses for Shirley Moog," with notes written on front of folder that read: "1969-70 Performance Synth (drawing of Min A modules in this!); Shipped to Keith Emerson, Sept. 70; Photos of early versions; Documents of instructions and modifications 1970-74."
    - ICA Live Performance Synth 2 of 2, 1967-1969 (Box 94, Folder 26B)
    - Perf Synth ICA production notes, winter 1969-1970, Winter (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Performance Synth instructions 1 of 2, Fall (Box 100, Folder 12)
      Original folder read: "Copy of instructions sent to Keith Emerson, Fall 1970, also Fall 1971."
    - Performance Synth instructions 2 of 2, Fall (Box 94, Folder 26C)
    - ICA Live Performance Synth 1 of 2, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - To be shipped with Keith Emerson's equipment, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Preset cards, 1973-07 (Box 94, Folder 26A)
    - Service manual for Keith Emerson's modular synthesizer, 1973-07 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Fairlight, 1982
    - Fairlight 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Fairlight 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Fairlight, 1982-09 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Flanger, 1976-11
    - Keyboard flanger 1 of 2, 1976-11 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Keyboard flanger 2 of 2, 1976-11 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Freeman String Symphonizer, 1977-04
    - Addition of resonant filters to Freeman String Symphonizer, 1977-04 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Frequency follower, 1972-04-1977-03
    - MI-76-005 frequency follower, 1976-04-1977-03 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Frequency follower 1 of 2, 1972-04-1972-06 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Frequency follower 2 of 2, 1972-04-1972-06 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Terry Fryer, 1983-10
    - Terry Fryer: Patch panel for Fairlight, 1983-10 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Glorious Chorus and Distortion, 1990-03-1990-12
    - Glorious Chorus, 1990-03-1990-12 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Glorious Distortion, 1990-12-23 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Guitar and Bass, 1976-1990
    - Guitar research and development 1 of 2, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      Includes materials documenting the Lab Series amplifiers, Gibson RD guitars, and various amplifiers, compressors, and equalizers.
    - Guitar research and development 1 of 2, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Guitar research and development 2 of 2, 1976-1977 (Mapcase-folder 6A)
    - Guitar research and development 2 of 2, 1976-1977 (Mapcase-folder 6B)
    - RD-77, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Guitar amp, 1976-03 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - MI-76-004 stereo string pickup, 1976-04 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - 200 watt amp, 1976-05 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Amp-002 GG5 100 watt guitar amp, 1976-05-1976-06 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Guitar amp, 1976-05 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Guitar amp circuitry 1 of 2, 1976-05-1976-10 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      Materials relating primarily to the G1, G3, and GG4 amplifiers.
    - Guitar amp circuitry 2 of 2, 1976-05-1976-10 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - General information on Gibson amplifier line development, 1976-07 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - SM-010 single band parametric tone booster - L-Series Amps, 1976-07-1977-02 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - G-1 preamp and 40 dB gain Budbox preamp, 1976-11 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - L-Series amps, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - RD-77 schematic bass/guitar modifier, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Compressor-expander for electric guitars and basses, 1977-03 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - RD77 notes, 1977-03 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - L-3 guitar amp, 1977-04-1977-05 (Mapcase-folder 5)
      Includes materials related to 300 PA head and the Lab Series L5, L7, and L9 amps.
    - Suggested procedure for checking out RD Artist electronics, using commercial test equipment, 1977-07 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Guitar second voice, 1977-11 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Guitar, distortion, chorus, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Jan Hammer, Undated
    - Modification to Jan Hammer instrument pre-amp, Undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Freeman modifications with multifilter for Jan Hammer, Undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Jan Hammer - Addition of inputs to #1125 sample and hold, Undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Hammond, 1940-1948
    - Hammond Solovox, 1940-1948 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      Owners manual and schematics/wiring diagram.
  - Eddie Harris, 1974-12-1978-03
    - Eddie Harris old attachment schematics 1 of 2, 1974-12-1976-07 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Eddie Harris old attachment schematics 2 of 2, 1974-12-1976-07 (Box 34, Folder 16A)
    - Eddie Harris - Distortion sustain project, 1975-09-1975-12 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Eddie Harris attachment, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Eddie Harris switch box, 1977-10-15 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Eddie Harris new attachment schematics 1 of 2, 1977-12-1978-03 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Eddie Harris new attachment schematics 2 of 2, 1977-12-1978-03 (Box 34, Folder 16B)
    - Eddie Harris attachment - user instructions - comments on tape ("new" attachment"), 1978-03 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Gershon Kingsley, 1969-1972-10
    - Kingsley I (1969 AES show live performance synth) 1 of 2, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Kingsley I (1969 AES show live performance synth) 2 of 2, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - 8364 Kingsley presets (engineering) 1 of 2, 1969-10-1972-10 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - 8364 Kingsley presets (engineering) 2 of 2, 1969-10-1972-10 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - A-440 oscillator comparator - Kingsley, 1970 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Kurzweil, 1984-1986
    - Out of date schematics - 8 key card and interface (Fatar keyboard) - K2 250, 1984-05-1984-06 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Schematics and parts list - interface board - K2 250 1 of 2, 1984-07-1984-09 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Schematics and parts list - interface board - K2 250 2 of 2, 1984-07-1984-09 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Kurzweil Ensemble Grande and MIDIBoard key velocity measurements, 1986-02-1986-06 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Lyra, 1973-03-1973-05
    - Lyra 0170-006, 1973-03-1973-05 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Lintronics, 1986-05-1995-06
    - LAMM, 1986-05-1994-12 (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - LAMM, 1992-06 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Old Big Briar LAMM instructions, 1992-06 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Old Rudi's LAMM instructions, 1992-07-1994-01 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Rudi Linhard/Lintronics, 1992-07-1995-06 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - LAMM serial #'s, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Lintronics MIDI converter, 1994-06 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - LAMM theory of operation, Undated (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - MRS
    - Berlant instruction manual, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - 1900 early work 1 of 2, 1968-06-1968-12 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - 1900 early work 2 of 2, 1968-06-1968-12 (Box 34, Folder 19A)
    - Dartmouth, 1968-07-1969-08 (Box 34, Folder 20B)
    - Moog 2-track overseas 1 of 2, 1968-07-1968-12 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Moog 2-track overseas 2 of 2, 1968-07-1968-12 (Box 34, Folder 19B)
    - Moog MRS - obsolete as of 3/15/70 1 of 2, 1968-07-1968-12 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      Original folder also reads: "Synch P.A. Location, Motor Plugs Longer."
    - Moog MRS - obsolete as of 3/15/70 2 of 2, 1968-07-1968-12 (Box 34, Folder 18C)
    - MRS binder #1 - 1 of 2, 1968-07-1971-04 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - MRS binder #1 - 2 of 2, 1968-07-1971-04 (Box 34, Folder 17A)
    - Vierra 8271 1 of 2, 1968-07-1970-03 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Vierra 8271 2 of 2, 1968-07-1970-03 (Box 34, Folder 18B)
    - Jobs and notes, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 30)
      Folder also reads: "#8092" and "Needs: P.S. ckt, repro ckt."
    - MRS - 8 track - (Moog studio), 1969 (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - Sales inquiries, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Tape recorder, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - MRS bias 1 of 2, 1969-05-1970-08 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - MRS bias 2 of 2, 1969-05-1970-08 (Box 34, Folder 19C)
    - Chad Hunt notebook I and II, 1969-06-1970-10 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1969-06-1969-11 (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - MRS schematics and notes 1 of 2, 1969-06-1970-08 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - MRS schematics and notes 2 of 2, 1969-06-1970-08 (Box 34, Folder 17C)
    - Southern Illinois University 1 of 2, 1969-08-1969-11 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Southern Illinois University 2 of 2, 1969-08-1969-11 (Box 34, Folder 19D)
    - U-Wash 290-042 8369, 1969-10-1970-10 (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Moog MRS 3/15/70, 1969-11-1969-12 (Box 34, Folder 18D)
    - Hampshire College 2-track, 1969-12-1970-01 (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Oberlin 4th play only 1 of 2, 1969-12 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Oberlin 4th play only 2 of 2, 1969-12 (Box 34, Folder 17D)
    - MRS instruction manual, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Remote box 4-track, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 21E)
    - MRS - 8 track Vierra - II production drawings 1 of 2, 1970-01-1970-06 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - MRS - 8 track Vierra - II production drawings 2 of 2, 1970-01-1970-06 (Box 34, Folder 18A)
    - AES prototype tape recorder mech. 1 of 2, 1970-02-1970-12 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - AES prototype tape recorder mech. 2 of 2, 1970-02-1970-12 (Box 34, Folder 18E)
    - Work for JLA 1 of 2, 1970-02 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Work for JLA 2 of 2, 1970-02 (Box 34, Folder 20A)
    - MRS binder #2 - 1 of 2, 1970-03-1970-09 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - MRS binder #2 - 2 of 2, 1970-03-1970-09 (Box 34, Folder 17B)
    - General MRS mech (working) 1 of 2, 1970-05-1970-08 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - General MRS mech (working) 2 of 2, 1970-05-1970-08 (Box 34, Folder 20D)
    - New Jersey Aluminum Company, 1970-05 (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - 4-track MRS recorder - University of Washington, 1970-06-1970-09 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - MRS switching 290-008, 1970-06-1970-09 (Box 90, Folder 35)
    - Master mock up (vector layouts) 1 of 2, 1970-08-1970-09 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Master mock up (vector layouts) 2 of 2, 1970-08-1970-09 (Box 34, Folder 20E)
    - MRS chts pre-drafting 1 of 2, 1970-08-1970-11 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - MRS chts pre-drafting 2 of 2, 1970-08-1970-11 (Box 34, Folder 21A)
    - Meter box 1 of 2, 1970-09 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Meter box 2 of 2, 1970-09 (Box 34, Folder 22C)
    - MRS power supply 1 of 2, 1970-09 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - MRS power supply 2 of 2, 1970-09 (Box 34, Folder 22D)
    - Rear conn assbly - 1) Wiring diag, 2) Connector pin locations 1 of 2, 1970-09 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Rear conn assbly - 1) Wiring diag, 2) Connector pin locations 2 of 2, 1970-09 (Box 34, Folder 22B)
    - Record module - 1) Drilling chart 2) PC notes and layouts 3) Pin diag (main board) 4) Mech parts diag 1 of 2, 1970-09-1970-10 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Record module - 1) Drilling chart 2) PC notes and layouts 3) Pin diag (main board) 4) Mech parts diag 2 of 2, 1970-09-1970-10 (Box 34, Folder 21C)
    - Preamp box - 1) Mechanical layout, 2) Wiring diagram, 1970-10 (Box 34, Folder 22A)
    - Preamp S- 1 of 2, 1970-10 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Preamp S- 2 of 2, 1970-10 (Box 34, Folder 21D)
    - Repro module - 1) Drilling chart 2) EQ card pin diagram 3) Main cord pin diagram 1 of 2, 1970-10 (Box 93, Folder 3)